Brian Adams

brian@brianadams.codes 937.602.8325

Website: <u>brianadams.codes</u> Github: @badams2527

Current Residence: Cincinnati, OH

Summary

Educated, efficient, self-motivated software developer with a wide range of past experience in various technologies. Strong communication skills allow for clients and co-workers to pose a problem and get a clear, effective solution in return. Able to gauge a situation from all different angles, and select the proper technology and implementation by not being "tied down" to any single one.

Education

University of Cincinnati (2012 – Current)

- Current GPA: 3.36
- Bachelor of Science in Computer Science
- Expected Graduation: 2017

Work Experience

Rippe & Kingston Systems, Inc. (October 2013 – Current)

- Co-manage a small team with a co-worker to build and maintain large-scale web applications
- Created development standards guideline for our team to use while developing
- Lead developer on an enterprise contract management application using C# and ASP.NET 4.5/MVC 4
- Lead developer on a large reporting application which was scalable and distributed using Python/Flask, RethinkDB, and AngularJS
- Successfully worked part-time and full-time hours while still remaining in school

ENSE (March 2012 - Current)

- Food equipment buying group in the UK
- Sole developer for the company www.enseuk.co.uk
- Design and develop entire web application from the ground up
- Use Node.JS, AngularJS, and RethinkDB to deliver a highly customizable and extensible user experience
- Interact with multiple people in the UK

UC Undergraduate Student Government (April 2015 – Current)

- Web Director In charge of all things web-related for Student Government
- Led team of three using Node.JS and MySQL to create a landlord rating and review system
- Use Knockout.js and Sammy.js to create a single page application framework with data-binding

Reynolds and Reynolds (April 2013 – August 2013)

- First professional corporate experience
- Developed internal web applications and WinForms applications using C#, JavaScript, and VB
- Gained experience in version control software (Microsoft Visual SourceSafe and SVN)

Activities

Theta Chi Fraternity (2013 – Current)

Founding Father

ACM@UC

Languages:

- JavaScript
- C#
- Python
- HTML
- CSS
- SQL
- C

Software/Frameworks:

- AngularJS
- ASP.NET
- SQL Server
- Node.JS
- RethinkDB
- Flask

Version Control:

- Git
- Subversion